



j.r.h.wood98@gmail.com



WHO AM I?

Forth-year engineering student majoring in Software. Finding an opportunity to apply and expand my knowledge. Highly motivated and ready to learn new things, with experience in the service industry and a passion for all things tech.



Kaggle Keras Tensorflow Sklearn Jupyter Weka



EXPERIENCE

2020 - Now Software Developer Internship part time

Niwa

My work experience involved developing a geographic information system (GIS). This used the Mapserver framework to create a web map service (WMS) to render data stored on a PostGIS database.

postgres / mapserver / linux

2018 - 2019 Bartender, Barista, Mixologist, Maitre D'

St. Johns Bar and Eatery

I furthered my communication skills from serving the upmarket clientele. This included supervising functions for Ministers of Parliament and their cabinets. We regularly hosted the staff for Xero and TradeMe.

conflict resolution / health and safety / customer service

2012 - 2018 Bartender, Barista, Kitchenhand Mac's Brewery

This was my first job. I started with no work experience and steadily progressed through the company. I learnt valuable communication, event coordination and conflict resolution skills. time management / communication

EDUCATION

2016 - Now **Batchelor of Engineering (Hons)** Victoria University of Wellington

Victoria Excellence Scholarship

Machine Learning, Mobile Software, Group Project, Game Dev

2011 - 2015 NCEA Level 3 endorsed with Excellence Rongotai

Scholarship English, Schools Canoe Polo

Prefect, UN Youth Ambassador, Debating, Rockquest, Jazz Band, Production Band

PROJECTS Data Ingestion

Python / Postgres /

GeoServer **Map Service**

Postgres / MapServer /

Apache MCS

React.js / Mapserver / Leaflet

HOBBIES

Sciences

CS, AI, Robotics, Astrophysics,

Psychology

Guitar

Classical, Jazz, Blues, Classic Rock

Sports

Canoe Polo, Table Tennis, Indoor Football

REFERENCES

Andrea Mari - Niwa

E: · Andea.Mari@niwa.co.nz

P: · 022434 2053

Tom Moorhead - Mac's

E: · tom@sscateriing.co.nz

P: · 0211395980

Troy Savage - Mac's

E: tsavage.nz@gmaill.com

P: · 0220657129